# **Henry Moule**

Software Developer Born 1995 in Bristol



## About me

Outside of work you'll find me working on my own coding projects, playing guitar (inside and outside church), going to the gym or browsing the internet for cute dogs. My main side projects in 2020 involved helping an overseas missionary develop a number of apps including a Bible verse of the day app called awal i wass (which roughly translates to word of God for each day) spoken in a language called Tashelhiyt. This app can be found on Google Play and the App Store and code for all the projects can be found here https://github.com/rd113267. My main side project at the moment involves working alongside and Personal trainer and osteopath to help develop an app called Health and Movement which is yet to be released but the code for which can be found

https://github.com/moulie415/HealthAndM

Also have experience in working in multiple Agile environments including experience working with Jira, Asana and Hive.

#### Skills



## Contact





## Experience

#### **JavaScript Developer**

CarePlanner Ltd Since November 2019

Working on the newest iteration of their mobile app using React Native which consumes a GraphQL api provided by AWS AppSync as a means to linking it to the CarePlanner REST api.

#### Software Developer

Active Inspiration Technologies

January 2018 - November 2019

For Active Inspiration I primarily worked on Fuell React Native app however I worked across the stack developing the fuell backend using Node.js and the Parse Server platform. Active Inspiration also had multiple clients who I have developed various solutions for using technologies including React, Node.js, GraphQL and Next.js.

## **Junior Software Developer**

**DYRNAN Communications** 

July 2017 - December 2017

I worked primarily on the frontend using React Native to develop their encrypted messaging app called Secoti (formerly Dyrnan).

## Freelance Web Developer

**Candour Creative** 

July 2016 - September 2016

Candour Creative outsourced some of their development work to me which involved developing the website nicksweeney.co.uk using WordPress as a platform to help develop them a custom CMS (PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, CSS).

#### **Support Representative**

WebCurl Ltd

November 2014 - June 2016

For my work placement at university I spent a year working for WebCurl (a Web Development Agency based in Oxford) where I helped develop their websites using Drupal (PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, CSS).



#### Education

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) Computer Science at Oxford Brookes University

2013 - 2017

4 year course (including a year in industry) teaching Java with a focus on OOP but also included many more modules that covered Python, C/C++, JavaScript and C#. My course also involved a teaching module where I spent a week as a teaching assistant helping teach Python and Scratch at a secondary school. In my final year as part of my final year project I developed a maths game that is currently available on the Google Play Store: play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mygdx.equationDragger

#### Queen Elizabeth's Hospital

2006 - 2013

A-levels: Mathematics (B), Music Technology (C), Religious Studies (C) GCSE's: 10 GCSE's including an A\* in music and A's in Maths, History, Biology, Chemistry, Physics and Religious Studies

→ hen10@hotmail.co.uk

07577635916

) johndoe.com

moulie415